{
    "question": "Tolong Beri Penjelasan Tentang Word Order\u00a0Dengan Rinci",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<span>Word order atau tata urut kata merupakan cara untuk\nmenyusun kata \u2013 kata dalam urutan atau susunan yang tepat dan benar. </span>\n\n<br><br><br><br>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "Word order adalah susunan kata-kata dalam kalimat, artinya bahwa cara kita menempatkan setiap kata itu haruslah sesuai dengan fungsinya dalam membentuk suatu kalimat. Caranya dengan mengetahui dan menghafal rumus atau pola baku.<br>Contoh:<br>&#039;&#039; Sebuah mobil mewah baru buatan Amerika Serikat &#039;&#039; diterjemahkan menjadi \" A new American car \".<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "choose-inappropriate-structure-in-the-following-sentences-or-dial-968",
            "question": "choose inappropriate structure in the following sentences or dialog below ! man : how's your new job at the hospital ? \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 A woman : it's great and my co-workers sre so nice \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 B \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 C man : good. that's important for you to feel exciting with your workers \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0D",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>man : good. that&#039;s important for you to feel <u>exciting</u> with your workers</span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "whats-is-the-problem-from-the-story-snow-bride-858",
            "question": "Whats is the problem from the story \"Snow Bride\"",
            "attachments": [
                "question-attachments/whats-is-the-problem-from-the-story-snow-bride-858-1.docx"
            ],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Carilah kata-kata yang terdengar janggal dan aneh... :)Mandiri lebih baik.<br>Okay ? @Liwed",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "in-pairscomplete-the-question-with-corret-simple-present-form-572",
            "question": "\u00a0in pairs,complete the question with corret simple present form. 1. A: ........ to the radio every morning? \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 B: Yes, I listen to it every morning \u00a0 2. A: .......... in Manchester\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 B: No, \u00a0he lives in Newcastle\u00a0 3. A: ......... the guitar?\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 B: Yes,she plays the guitar and the piano.\u00a0 4. A: \u00a0......... TV every morning?\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 B: No,they watch is most evening.\u00a0 5. A: \u00a0......... To school every day?\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 B: She usually goes to school at 06.00 a.m. .",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. do<br>2. does he<br>3. does she play<br>4. do they watch<br>5. what time does she usually go",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "1.\u00a0do you<br>2. does he live<br>3. does she play<br>4. do they watch<br>5. what time does she usually go",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-dialog-bahasa-inggris-tentang-expressing-threateningthrea-780",
            "question": "Contoh dialog bahasa inggris tentang expressing threatening/threat ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "A : Hey, when do you want to pay your debt?<br>B : I will do my best to pay it next week.<br>A : It&#039;s better for you to keep your words, otherwise Don Corleone will kill you\u00a0<br>B : DOn&#039;t worry sir, I will keep my words",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-percakapan-expression-care-826",
            "question": "Contoh percakapan expression care",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "how poor you are<br>what a pity<br>i am sorry to hear that",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Situation : Your friend is sad.<br><br>Ana : <strong>Are you okay? You look so sad.</strong><br>Nia : <em>No, I&#039;m not okay.</em> I feel so sad because I had a fight with my brother yesterday.<br>Ana : Why?<br>Nia : He took my favorite novel without asking my permission and he ripped it! How can I not sad? He even not sorry at all and when I yelled at him, he yelled me back with his ridiculous reason that why should I got sad over a novel!<br>Ana : You must be really hurt...<br>Nia : Of couse I do.<br>Ana : <strong>What should I do to cheer you up?</strong><br>Nia : <em>Thanks for your attention</em> but no, sorry.<br>Ana : <strong>Really?</strong> I&#039;m sorry I can&#039;t help you much.<br>Nia: <em>Yeah, thanks</em>.<br><br><strong>bold: expressions<br></strong><em>italic: responses</em><strong><br></strong>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-text-hartatory-explenation-yang-berjudul-effect-of-insomni-716",
            "question": "Buat text hartatory explenation \u00a0yang berjudul effect of insomnia",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Effect of Insomnia<br>Horatory -&gt; thesis -&gt; reason -&gt; suggestion<br><br>Insomnia is kind of illness that makes people hard to sleep. Due to its negative effect, this illness is categorized as the dangerous symptoms. The reason could be classified from Internal feelings of the person. Therefore if we have this illness, better to have consultation toward the doctor. We stand to benefit by the greater time of sleep that we have.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bantuin-aku-dong-cari-biografi-aknes-monica-menggunakan-bahasa-in-292",
            "question": "Bantuin aku dong cari Biografi aknes monica menggunakan Bahasa inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Agnes Monica Muljoto. Born in Jakarta 1 July 1986, known abroad as Agnes Mo. She stared her career in the entertainment industry at the age of six as a child singer. She jobs is singer, actress, dancer, voice actress, and producer.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-bahasa-inggrisnya-mengacak-acak-rambutnya-667",
            "question": "Apa Bahasa Inggrisnya mengacak-acak rambutnya?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "bahasa inggris nya adalah mess her/his hair",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Ruffled/Mess his/her hair<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "terjemahan-teks-the-spying-parrot-892",
            "question": "Terjemahan teks the spying parrot",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Ini terjemahannnya<br>Mata-Mata burung beo <br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "mata-mata burung beo",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-berikan-contoh-dialogue-4-orang-yang-didalam-dialogue-ters-769",
            "question": "tolong berikan contoh dialogue 4 orang yang didalam dialogue tersebut terdapat expressing love ,expressing\u00a0sadness ,expressing\u00a0embarrassment ,expressing attitudes towards something and ,expressing\u00a0anger snd annoyance.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "A: i love you<br>B: i love you too but i can&#039;t to be with you. i&#039;m sorry",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}